SUMMARY

Offering over five years' experience working in software development, web content management, eLearning courseware, web fundamentals coaching, and business operations.

I have a passion for creating inclusive experiences, relying on accessibility standards and user experience.

CONTACT

PHONE: 425-773-8165

WEBSITE: victorswanberg.dev

EMAIL: Victorswanberg89@gmail.com

ESSENTIAL QUALITIES

Coding
People development
Communication
Design
User experience

VICTOR SWANBERG

Web Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sublime Media - Web Developer

2018 - Present

- Design and develop innovative web applications that draw the user's attention
- Build modular and reusable components and libraries
- Implement front-end components with progressive Vue.js framework
- Create custom stylesheets to deliver a polished designed product with CSS and SCSS
- Ensuring product works with assistive technologies
- Translate the client's technical specifications into code
- Test, update and optimize the application for performance and security

Nucamp - Instructor

2021 - Present

- Facilitate and teach online courses
- Create projects and small code environments to test users' knowledge
- Provide a positive learning experience while reenforcing industry standards
- One on one coaching with students and syntax feedback

Philip J Boren Inc. - Account Manager

2017 - 2018

- Troubleshooted any IT related issues in an office environment
- Maintained company website
- Deployed workstations for new employees

EDUCATION

Edmonds Community College - 2015

ATA of Computer Information Systems Desktop support specialist certificate Database management certificate Network security certificate

Nucamp - 2020

Web fundamentals certificate
Front-end developer program certificate